Guide to the International Brotherhood of Teamsters Leo Deaner collection 1902-2006 IBT0022
Special Collections Research Center, The George Washington University
- Project RISE, 1992-2005; 1999-2005; Series 5; 4.5 Linear Feet
  - Code of Conduct, 2000-2001; Series 5 Subseries 1; 1 Linear Feet
    - Official Draft No. 1, undated; Series 5 Subseries 1 (Box 29, Folder 9)
    - Official Draft No. 2, 2000 September 25; Series 5 Subseries 1 (Box 30, Folder 1)
    - Discussion Draft, 2000 October 31; Series 5 Subseries 1 (Box 30, Folder 2)
    - "Red-Line" Drafts, 2000 December 18; Series 5 Subseries 1 (Box 30, Folder 3)
    - "Red-Line" Drafts, 2001 February 9; Series 5 Subseries 1 (Box 30, Folder 4)
    - "Red-Line" Drafts, 2001 March 13; Series 5 Subseries 1 (Box 30, Folder 5)
  - The Teamsters and Organized Crime Report, 2001-2002; Series 5 Subseries 2; 2 Linear Feet
    This subseries contains drafts and final copies of a report, commissioned by Project RISE and prepared by the law firm Stier, Anderson & Malone, LLC, on the history and perception of organized crime's influence on the International Brotherhood of Teamsters. Included are the main text of the report as well as public and confidential appendices. Over 500 pages long and split into 26 chapters, the report covers the entire history of the Teamsters, the state of organized crime in the union at the time of writing, and recommendations to Project RISE about how to run a clean union in the future.
    This subseries is arranged chronologically.
    - The Teamsters and Organized Crime - Draft 1 [1/7], 2001; Series 5 Subseries 2 (Box 31, Folder 1)
    - The Teamsters and Organized Crime - Draft 1 [2/7], 2001; Series 5 Subseries 2 (Box 31, Folder 2)
    - The Teamsters and Organized Crime - Draft 1 [3/7], 2001; Series 5 Subseries 2 (Box 31, Folder 3)
    - The Teamsters and Organized Crime - Draft 1 [4/7], 2001; Series 5 Subseries 2 (Box 31, Folder 4)
    - The Teamsters and Organized Crime - Draft 1 [5/7], 2001; Series 5 Subseries 2 (Box 31, Folder 5)
    - The Teamsters and Organized Crime - Draft 1 [6/7], 2001; Series 5 Subseries 2 (Box 31, Folder 6)
    - The Teamsters and Organized Crime - Draft 1 [7/7], 2001; Series 5 Subseries 2 (Box 31, Folder 7)
    - The Teamsters and Organized Crime - Draft 2 [1/3], 2001; Series 5 Subseries 2 (Box 32, Folder 1)
    - The Teamsters and Organized Crime - Draft 2 [2/3], 2001; Series 5 Subseries 2 (Box 32, Folder 2)
    - The Teamsters and Organized Crime - Draft 2 [3/3], 2001; Series 5 Subseries 2 (Box 32, Folder 3)
    - The Teamsters and Organized Crime: Table of Contents, Introduction and Summary of Conclusions, 2002; Series 5 Subseries 2 (Box 32, Folder 4)
    - The Teamsters and Organized Crime: Part I [1/3], 2002; Series 5 Subseries 2 (Box 32, Folder 5)
    - The Teamsters and Organized Crime: Part I [2/3], 2002; Series 5 Subseries 2 (Box 32, Folder 6)
    - The Teamsters and Organized Crime: Part I [3/3], 2002; Series 5 Subseries 2 (Box 32, Folder 7)
    - The Teamsters and Organized Crime: Part II [1/2], 2002; Series 5 Subseries 2 (Box 33, Folder 1)
    - The Teamsters and Organized Crime: Part II [2/2], 2002; Series 5 Subseries 2 (Box 33, Folder 2)
    - The Teamsters and Organized Crime - Appendix I: Background Materials [1/3], 2002; Series 5 Subseries 2 (Box 33, Folder 3)
    - The Teamsters and Organized Crime - Appendix I: Background Materials [2/3], 2002; Series 5 Subseries 2 (Box 33, Folder 4)
    - The Teamsters and Organized Crime - Appendix I: Background Materials [3/3], 2002; Series 5 Subseries 2 (Box 33, Folder 5)
    - The Teamsters: Perception and Reality, 2002; Series 5 Subseries 2 (Box 33, Folder 6)
    - The Teamsters: Perception and Reality - Summary of Report, 2002; Series 5 Subseries 2 (Box 34, Folder 1)
    - The Teamsters: Perception and Reality - Appendix I: Background Materials, 2002; Series 5 Subseries 2 (Box 34, Folder 2)
    - The Teamsters: Perception and Reality - Confidential Appendix 2: Summary of Field Results Vol. 1 [1/2], 2002; Series 5 Subseries 2 (Box 34, Folder 3)
    - The Teamsters: Perception and Reality - Confidential Appendix 2: Summary of Field Results Vol. 1 [2/2], 2002; Series 5 Subseries 2 (Box 34, Folder 4)
    - The Teamsters: Perception and Reality - Confidential Appendix 2: Summary of Field Results Vol. 2 [1/2], 2002; Series 5 Subseries 2 (Box 34, Folder 5)
    - The Teamsters: Perception and Reality - Confidential Appendix 2: Summary of Field Results Vol. 2 [2/2], 2002; Series 5 Subseries 2 (Box 34, Folder 6)
  - General Files, 1992-2005; 1999-2005; Series 5 Subseries 3; 1.5 Linear Feet
    This subseries is arranged in its original order.
    This subseries contains materials related to the work of Project RISE, with most dating from 1999-2005. Specifically, most of the materials cover the founding of the Project, the creation of the Code of Conduct, and the Teamsters and Organized Crime Reprt. Included are news clippings, memos and correspondence, newsletters, reports and hearing transcripts.
    - Edwin Stier - Correspondence and News Clippings, 1999-2005; Series 5 Subseries 3 (Box 35, Folder 1)
    - Edwin Stier - Resignation, 2004; Series 5 Subseries 3 (Box 35, Folder 2)
    - Edwin Stier / Patrick Symanski Correspondence, 2003-2004; Series 5 Subseries 3 (Box 35, Folder 3)
    - Edward McDonald, 2004-2005; Series 5 Subseries 3 (Box 35, Folder 4)
    - 26th International Convention RISE Resolution, 2002; Series 5 Subseries 3 (Box 35, Folder 5)
    - United States Attorney - Correspondence, 2000; Series 5 Subseries 3 (Box 35, Folder 6)
    - Employee Benefit Plans, 2000; Series 5 Subseries 3 (Box 35, Folder 7)
    - Thomas Puccio - News Clippings, 2001; Series 5 Subseries 3 (Box 35, Folder 8)
    - Ron Teninty - Correspondence, 2000; Series 5 Subseries 3 (Box 35, Folder 9)
    - Project RISE Task Force Members and Joint Council Coordinators, undated; Series 5 Subseries 3 (Box 35, Folder 10)
    - Project RISE Advisory Board Meeting, 2000; Series 5 Subseries 3 (Box 35, Folder 11)
    - Left-Wing Press Articles, 2000; Series 5 Subseries 3 (Box 35, Folder 12)
    - Notes, 2002; Series 5 Subseries 3 (Box 35, Folder 13)
    - Organized Crime Report - News Clippings, 2002-2003; Series 5 Subseries 3 (Box 35, Folder 14)
    - Association for Union Democracy Convention, 2000; Series 5 Subseries 3 (Box 35, Folder 15)
    - "Union Democracy Review" Newsletter, 2001-2002; Series 5 Subseries 3 (Box 35, Folder 16)
    - Teamsters for a Democratic Union, 2000-2001; Series 5 Subseries 3 (Box 35, Folder 17)
    - Edwin Stier - Appointment, 1999; Series 5 Subseries 3 (Box 35, Folder 18)
    - Joint Council No. 40 - Correspondence, 2001; Series 5 Subseries 3 (Box 35, Folder 19)
    - Gary Witlen - Code of Conduct Comments, 2003; Series 5 Subseries 3 (Box 35, Folder 20)
    - Gerry Miller - Code of Conduct Comments, 2000; Series 5 Subseries 3 (Box 35, Folder 21)
    - National Organized Crime Field Study, 2000-2001; Series 5 Subseries 3 (Box 35, Folder 22)
    - Joint Council Leadership, 2000; Series 5 Subseries 3 (Box 35, Folder 23)
    - Anti-Corruption Initiative, 1999; Series 5 Subseries 3 (Box 35, Folder 24)
    - The Teamster Magazine, 1999 October; Series 5 Subseries 3 (Box 35, Folder 25)
    - Harris Hartz, 1999; Series 5 Subseries 3 (Box 35, Folder 26)
    - Leo Deaner / Edwin Stier Discussion, 2000-2002; Series 5 Subseries 3 (Box 35, Folder 27)
    - Teamsters General Executive Board Resolution, 1999; Series 5 Subseries 3 (Box 35, Folder 28)
    - Project RISE Survey, undated; Series 5 Subseries 3 (Box 35, Folder 29)
    - Ethics Consultants, 2000; Series 5 Subseries 3 (Box 35, Folder 30)
    - Robert Luskin, 2001-2003; Series 5 Subseries 3 (Box 35, Folder 31)
    - AFL-CIO Resolution, 1992; Series 5 Subseries 3 (Box 35, Folder 32)
    - Organized Crime Report, 2002; Series 5 Subseries 3 (Box 35, Folder 33)
    - "The Teamsters and Organized Crime" Summary of Report, 2002; Series 5 Subseries 3 (Box 35, Folder 34)
    - James P. Hoffa - Organized Crime Report Speech, 2002; Series 5 Subseries 3 (Box 35, Folder 35)
    - Organized Crime Report - News Clippings, 2002; Series 5 Subseries 3 (Box 35, Folder 36)
    - Donato Desanti / Local 107, 2002-2005; Series 5 Subseries 3 (Box 36, Folder 1)
    - Donato Desanti / Local 107 / TJ Maxx, 1999-2003; Series 5 Subseries 3 (Box 36, Folder 2)
    - Frank Walsh Wiretap Transcripts [1/2], 2002; Series 5 Subseries 3 (Box 36, Folder 3)
    - Frank Walsh Wiretap Transcripts [2/2], 2002; Series 5 Subseries 3 (Box 36, Folder 4)
    - Local Union Leader Profiles, undated; Series 5 Subseries 3 (Box 36, Folder 5)
    - Confidential Report Re: Allegations in April 2004 Report by Stier Anderson, LLC, 2005; Series 5 Subseries 3 (Box 36, Folder 6)
    - Public Report Re: Allegations in April 2004 Report by Stier Anderson, LLC, 2005; Series 5 Subseries 3 (Box 36, Folder 7)
    - Draft Report Tre Allegations in April 2004 Report by Stier Anderson, LLC [1/2], 2005; Series 5 Subseries 3 (Box 36, Folder 8)
    - Draft Report Tre Allegations in April 2004 Report by Stier Anderson, LLC [2/2], 2005; Series 5 Subseries 3 (Box 36, Folder 9)
    - Report: "Issues Concerning Chicago Organized Crime Infiltration of Teamster Entities and Attempts to Undermine IBT Anti-Racketeering Reforms", 2004 April; Series 5 Subseries 3 (Box 36, Folder 10)
    - Report: "Issues Concerning Chicago Organized Crime Infiltration of Teamster Entities and Attempts to Undermine IBT Anti-Racketeering Reforms" Appendix, 2004 April; Series 5 Subseries 3 (Box 37, Folder 1)
    - "Report of Investigation into Allegations of Prohibited Association with Organized Crime Figure and Failure to Cooperate: Local 786 Chicago, Illinois", 2003; Series 5 Subseries 3 (Box 37, Folder 2)
- Personal/Family Files, 1937-2007; Series 6; 3.75 Linear Feet
  This series is arranged alphabetically.
  This series contains Leo Deaner's personal and family-related files. The included materials date from 1937-2007 and mostly cover Deaner's family history, with a particular focus on his father, IBT Local 776 member Charles E. Deaner. Specific materials contained in the series include numerous photographs, correspondence, news clippings, collected family documents (e.g. birth/death certificates), IBT Local 776 history, and company history. Also included are various pieces of ephemera mostly related to Charles Deaner, including safe driver cards and pins, convention delegate pins and ribbons, awards, and Deaner's World War II dog tags.
  - 401st Bombardment Group, 1940s; Series 6 (Box 38, Folder 1)
  - 612th Bombardment Squadron History, undated; Series 6 (Box 38, Folder 2)
  - 1961 IBT Convention, 1961 July 3; Series 6 (Box 38, Folder 3)
  - Arthur Markovitz, 1980-1996; Series 6 (Box 38, Folder 4)
  - Charles E. Deaner [1/5], 1971-1977; Series 6 (Box 38, Folder 5)
  - Charles E. Deaner [2/5], 1957-1999; Series 6 (Box 38, Folder 6)
  - Charles E. Deaner [3/5], 1952-1984; Series 6 (Box 38, Folder 7)
  - Charles E. Deaner [4/5], 1938-1999; Series 6 (Box 38, Folder 8)
  - Charles E. Deaner [5/5], 1993 January 19; Series 6 (Box 38, Folder 9)
  - Charles E. Deaner - Dues Books, 1940-1955; Series 6 (Box 38, Folder 10)
  - Charles E. Deaner - Order of the Purple Heart, 1950s; Series 6 (Box 38, Folder 11)
  - Charles E. Deaner - World War II Service, 1945-2007; Series 6 (Box 38, Folder 12)
  - Deaner Family History, undated; Series 6 (Box 38, Folder 13)
  - Deaner Family Photographs, undated; Series 6 (Box 38, Folder 14)
  - Elsie Mae McGarr Deaner, undated; Series 6 (Box 38, Folder 15)
  - Follmer Trucking Company, 1966-1970; Series 6 (Box 38, Folder 16)
  - Harrisburg, PA Bicentennial Parade, 1976; Series 6 (Box 38, Folder 17)
  - IBT Local 776 [1/2], 1937-1993; Series 6 (Box 38, Folder 18)
  - IBT Local 776 [2/2], 1937-1999; Series 6 (Box 38, Folder 19)
  - Norwalk Truck Lines, 1951-1963; Series 6 (Box 38, Folder 20)
  - Pennsylvania Veterans' Memorial Dedication, 2001; Series 6 (Box 38, Folder 21)
  - Shirks Motor Express Corp., 1954-1981; Series 6 (Box 38, Folder 22)
  - Teamsters DRIVE, 1964-1984; Series 6 (Box 39, Folder 1)
  - Teamsters Federal Credit Union, 1950-1958; Series 6 (Box 39, Folder 2)
  - Miscellaneous, 1970s; Series 6 (Box 39, Folder 3)
  - Artifacts [1/3], 1940s-1950s; Series 6 (Oversize 40)
    General
    This box contains Charles E. Deaner's safe driver cards, pins, and his World War II dog tags.
  - Artifacts [2/3], 1970s-1990s; Series 6 (Oversize 41)
    This box contains Charles E. Deaner's IBT Convention delegate pins and ribbons, and two of his personalized belt buckles.
  - Artifacts [3/3], 1961-1976; Series 6 (Oversize 42)
    This box contains two framed sets of photographs and Charles E. Deaner's IBT Convention Delegate pin and ribbon.
- Pennsylvania Local Union Files, 1950-2006; Series 7; 1.5 Linear Feet
  This series contains documentation on a number of Pennsylvania IBT local unions and local union officers.
  Series 7 is arranged by local or individual local officer.
  - Orginial Box List for Pennsylvania Local Unions, Undated; Series 7 (Box 63, Folder 1)
  - Local 771, Undated; Series 7 (Box 63, Folder 2)
  - The Philadelphia Inquirer Business Page, 2004 September 6; Series 7 (Box 63, Folder 3)
  - Local 463- Ryder, Undated; Series 7 (Box 63, Folder 4)
  - Local 107- Ray Cohen, 1984 July 17; Series 7 (Box 63, Folder 5)
  - Local 107 Bottone-Sheeran, 1979-1980; Series 7 (Box 63, Folder 6)
  - 107 Lawsuit, 1987-1988, 1992; Series 7 (Box 63, Folder 7)
  - Local 107- Hamilton, 1999-2001; Series 7 (Box 63, Folder 8)
  - Local 107- The Voice, 1989, 1995; Series 7 (Box 63, Folder 9)
  - Local 107- Dooley Team, 2005; Series 7 (Box 63, Folder 10)
  - Local 107- Convention Center, 1993, 2000-2001; Series 7 (Box 63, Folder 11)
  - Local 107- Cimino, 1991, 2000; Series 7 (Box 63, Folder 12)
  - Local 107- Ryan, 1992, 1996; Series 7 (Box 63, Folder 13)
  - Local 107- Ryan, 1996, 1999; Series 7 (Box 63, Folder 14)
  - Local 107- Ryan, 1996; Series 7 (Box 63, Folder 15)
  - Lou Polities (156), 1979, 1984-1985; Series 7 (Box 63, Folder 16)
  - Local 158, 1984, 1987; Series 7 (Box 63, Folder 17)
  - Duckenfield, B.161, Undated; Series 7 (Box 63, Folder 18)
  - Local 169, 1982; Series 7 (Box 63, Folder 19)
  - Local 211, 1989, 1991, 2000; Series 7 (Box 63, Folder 20)
  - Joe Molinero (211), 1992-1993; Series 7 (Box 63, Folder 21)
  - Joe Molinero (211), 1990, 1992; Series 7 (Box 63, Folder 22)
  - Joe Mecca (229), 1992, 1994; Series 7 (Box 63, Folder 23)
  - Tom Fagan (249), 1979 August 12; Series 7 (Box 63, Folder 24)
  - Local 331, 1985, 1987, 2002; Series 7 (Box 63, Folder 25)
  - Local 331, 1990, 1993-1994, 1999-2002; Series 7 (Box 63, Folder 26)
  - Snead, Bill 384, 1987, 1992; Series 7 (Box 63, Folder 27)
  - Local 401, 1974, 1985, 1990; Series 7 (Box 63, Folder 28)
  - Leo Namey (401), 1974, 1984, 2003; Series 7 (Box 63, Folder 29)
  - Earls (402), 1999, 2002; Series 7 (Box 63, Folder 30)
  - Schell- 429, 1950, 2001; Series 7 (Box 63, Folder 31)
  - Kistler- 429, Undated; Series 7 (Box 63, Folder 32)
  - Burns- 429, 1978, 1984, 1990; Series 7 (Box 63, Folder 33)
  - Rochowicz- 429, 1999; Series 7 (Box 63, Folder 34)
  - Nangle- 429, 1970, 1972, 1974, 1978; Series 7 (Box 63, Folder 35)
  - Fasig- 429, 1983 March 23; Series 7 (Box 63, Folder 36)
  - Cicak, Kevin 430, 2002, 2004; Series 7 (Box 64, Folder 1)
  - Al Linebaugh (430), 1956, 1965; Series 7 (Box 64, Folder 2)
  - Stocker- 430, 1977, 1992, 1994-1995; Series 7 (Box 64, Folder 3)
  - 430- Al Koch, 2003 March 29; Series 7 (Box 64, Folder 4)
  - 491, 2002 March 8; Series 7 (Box 64, Folder 5)
  - Local 500, 1968, 1980s, 1990s, 2003-2004, 2006; Series 7 (Box 64, Folder 6)
  - Dan McGinley (502), 1986-1987, 1993; Series 7 (Box 64, Folder 7)
  - Local 513, 1984, 2005; Series 7 (Box 64, Folder 8)
  - Gullifer, Bill 628, 1985, 1988; Series 7 (Box 64, Folder 9)
  - Local 676- Dockworkers 1, 1989, 1993-1996, 1998-1999, 2002; Series 7 (Box 64, Folder 10)
  - Local 676, 1979, 1989-1991, 2000-2002; Series 7 (Box 64, Folder 11)
  - John Greeley 676, 1966; Series 7 (Box 64, Folder 12)
  - Local 676, 2002-2003; Series 7 (Box 64, Folder 13)
  - 676, 2002-2004; Series 7 (Box 64, Folder 14)
  - Landis/Yeakel-773, 1990-1993; Series 7 (Box 64, Folder 15)
  - Dipietro/Franks-773, 1995, 1997; Series 7 (Box 64, Folder 16)
  - Banus- 773, 1976; Series 7 (Box 64, Folder 17)
  - Joint Council (JC) 53 Smut Sheets, 2002-2003; Series 7 (Box 64, Folder 18)
  - 2002- Smut Sheets, 1999, 2001-2002; Series 7 (Box 64, Folder 19)
  - 2002- JC 53, 2001 November 5; Series 7 (Box 64, Folder 20)
  - 2001- TJ Maxx, Series 7 (Box 64, Folder 21)
  - 2000/2001 JC 53 Smut, 2000-2001, 2006; Series 7 (Box 64, Folder 22)
- Teamster Election Files, 1991-1996; Series 8; 12 Linear Feet
  This series contains documentation on four IBT elections.
  Series 8 is arranged chronologically by lection date.
  - 1991 Election, 1990-1992; Series 8 Subseries 1
    - Original Box List for 1991 IBT Election, Undated; Series 8 Subseries 1 (Box 64, Folder 23)
    - Protest- Reimbursement, 1991; Series 8 Subseries 1 (Box 64, Folder 24)
    - IBT Election- Harrisburg, 1991; Series 8 Subseries 1 (Box 64, Folder 25)
    - Desk- Literature, 1991; Series 8 Subseries 1 (Box 64, Folder 26)
    - Lacey Decision, 1991; Series 8 Subseries 1 (Box 64, Folder 27)
    - Griffith Appeal, 1991; Series 8 Subseries 1 (Box 64, Folder 28)
    - Holland Decision, 1991; Series 8 Subseries 1 (Box 64, Folder 29)
    - Marks Visit, 1991; Series 8 Subseries 1 (Box 64, Folder 30)
    - Protest- Deaner, 1991; Series 8 Subseries 1 (Box 64, Folder 31)
    - Smart Protest, 1991; Series 8 Subseries 1 (Box 64, Folder 32)
    - 776 Newsletter, 1991; Series 8 Subseries 1 (Box 64, Folder 33)
    - St. J. Protest, 1991; Series 8 Subseries 1 (Box 65, Folder 1)
    - Ballot- 776 Delegate, 1991; Series 8 Subseries 1 (Box 65, Folder 2)
    - Carey- Harrisburg, 1991; Series 8 Subseries 1 (Box 65, Folder 3)
    - Deaner Endorsement, 1991; Series 8 Subseries 1 (Box 65, Folder 4)
    - Durham- Harrisburg, 1991; Series 8 Subseries 1 (Box 65, Folder 5)
    - 776 Executive-Board, 1991; Series 8 Subseries 1 (Box 65, Folder 6)
    - 1991/776 Delegate Election Results, Series 8 Subseries 1 (Box 65, Folder 7)
    - Protests- Before, 1991; Series 8 Subseries 1 (Box 65, Folder 8)
    - 1991/776 Delegate Protests After, Series 8 Subseries 1 (Box 65, Folder 9)
    - 1991 Delegate Election- Fike Ticket, Series 8 Subseries 1 (Box 65, Folder 10)
    - 1991 Delegate Election - TFT Ticket, Series 8 Subseries 1 (Box 65, Folder 11)
    - Newspapers- June 1991, Series 8 Subseries 1 (Box 65, Folder 12)
    - Press- June 1991, Series 8 Subseries 1 (Box 65, Folder 13)
    - Griffith Endorsement, 1991; Series 8 Subseries 1 (Box 65, Folder 14)
    - 1991 Delegate Election- Kohr Ticket, Series 8 Subseries 1 (Box 65, Folder 15)
    - Newspapers- June 1991, Series 8 Subseries 1 (Box 65, Folder 16)
    - 1990 Newspapers, Series 8 Subseries 1 (Box 65, Folder 17)
    - Labor Notes- Before and During Convention, 1991; Series 8 Subseries 1 (Box 65, Folder 18)
    - Press- January-May 1991, Series 8 Subseries 1 (Box 65, Folder 19)
    - Teamsters for a Democratic Union (TDU), 1991; Series 8 Subseries 1 (Box 65, Folder 20)
    - Association for Union Democracy (AUD)- Before and During Convention, 1991; Series 8 Subseries 1 (Box 65, Folder 21)
    - "Left" Journals- Before and During Convention, 1991; Series 8 Subseries 1 (Box 65, Folder 22)
    - Press- July- November 1991, Series 8 Subseries 1 (Box 65, Folder 23)
    - Press- December 1991 Election Results, Series 8 Subseries 1 (Box 65, Folder 24)
    - Durham Literature, 1991; Series 8 Subseries 1 (Box 65, Folder 25)
    - Durham Literature, 1991; Series 8 Subseries 1 (Box 65, Folder 26)
    - Post Mark, 1991; Series 8 Subseries 1 (Box 65, Folder 27)
    - Kane, 1991; Series 8 Subseries 1 (Box 65, Folder 28)
    - Durham Delegate Election, 1991; Series 8 Subseries 1 (Box 65, Folder 29)
    - Durham Delegate Election, 1991; Series 8 Subseries 1 (Box 65, Folder 30)
    - Delegate Election Smut, 1991; Series 8 Subseries 1 (Box 65, Folder 31)
    - Carey Ticket Delegate Election, 1991; Series 8 Subseries 1 (Box 66, Folder 1)
    - Trustee Candidates- Durham, 1991; Series 8 Subseries 1 (Box 66, Folder 2)
    - Trustee Candidates- Shea, 1991; Series 8 Subseries 1 (Box 66, Folder 3)
    - Swearing In 1992, Series 8 Subseries 1 (Box 66, Folder 4)
    - Campaign Advisories, 1991; Series 8 Subseries 1 (Box 66, Folder 5)
    - The New Teamsters Materials, 1992; Series 8 Subseries 1 (Box 66, Folder 6)
    - Morris, 1991; Series 8 Subseries 1 (Box 66, Folder 7)
    - Results, 1991; Series 8 Subseries 1 (Box 66, Folder 8)
    - After Election Protest, 1992; Series 8 Subseries 1 (Box 66, Folder 9)
    - Ballot, 1991; Series 8 Subseries 1 (Box 66, Folder 10)
    - 1991 IBT Delegates, Series 8 Subseries 1 (Box 66, Folder 11)
    - Shea Poll, 1991; Series 8 Subseries 1 (Box 66, Folder 12)
    - Shea/Ligurotis Slate, 1991; Series 8 Subseries 1 (Box 66, Folder 13)
    - Convention Campaign Smut, 1991; Series 8 Subseries 1 (Box 66, Folder 14)
    - Durham Unity Team, 1991; Series 8 Subseries 1 (Box 66, Folder 15)
    - Riga, 1991; Series 8 Subseries 1 (Box 66, Folder 16)
    - Independent Candidates, 1991; Series 8 Subseries 1 (Box 66, Folder 17)
    - Hoffa, James P., 1991; Series 8 Subseries 1 (Box 66, Folder 18)
    - Racketeer Influenced and Corrupt Organizations Act (RICO), 1991; Series 8 Subseries 1 (Box 66, Folder 19)
    - Ligurotis, 1991; Series 8 Subseries 1 (Box 66, Folder 20)
    - Carey Slate, 1991; Series 8 Subseries 1 (Box 67, Folder 1)
    - Travel and Lodging, 1991; Series 8 Subseries 1 (Box 67, Folder 2)
    - Resolutions, 1991; Series 8 Subseries 1 (Box 67, Folder 3)
    - Officers Report, 1991; Series 8 Subseries 1 (Box 67, Folder 4)
    - Election Officer, 1991; Series 8 Subseries 1 (Box 67, Folder 5)
    - Convention News, 1991; Series 8 Subseries 1 (Box 67, Folder 6)
    - 2000- 2 Million, 1991; Series 8 Subseries 1 (Box 67, Folder 7)
    - Constitution, 1991; Series 8 Subseries 1 (Box 67, Folder 8)
    - Carey Literature, 1991; Series 8 Subseries 1 (Box 67, Folder 9)
    - Carey Mailing, 1991; Series 8 Subseries 1 (Box 67, Folder 10)
    - Durham Mailing, 1991; Series 8 Subseries 1 (Box 67, Folder 11)
    - The Teamsters, 1991; Series 8 Subseries 1 (Box 67, Folder 12)
    - Durham Communications, 1991; Series 8 Subseries 1 (Box 67, Folder 13)
    - Feinstein, 1991; Series 8 Subseries 1 (Box 67, Folder 14)
    - McCarthy, 1991; Series 8 Subseries 1 (Box 67, Folder 15)
    - Mathis, 1991; Series 8 Subseries 1 (Box 67, Folder 16)
    - Shea Ligurotis Literature, 1991; Series 8 Subseries 1 (Box 67, Folder 17)
    - Shea/Ligurotis Literature, 1991; Series 8 Subseries 1 (Box 67, Folder 18)
    - Joe 'T', 1991; Series 8 Subseries 1 (Box 67, Folder 19)
    - Saporta, 1991; Series 8 Subseries 1 (Box 67, Folder 20)
    - Rules Committee, 1991; Series 8 Subseries 1 (Box 67, Folder 21)
    - The Teamster Magazine, 1991; Series 8 Subseries 1 (Box 67, Folder 22)
    - Durham Poll, 1991; Series 8 Subseries 1 (Box 67, Folder 23)
    - 1991- Morris Election, Series 8 Subseries 1 (Box 67, Folder 24)
    - Rules for the IBT Officer Election, 1990; Series 8 Subseries 1 (Box 67, Folder 25)
  - 1996 Election, 1976-1998; Series 8 Subseries 2
    - Original Box List for 1996 Rerun Election, Undated; Series 8 Subseries 2 (Box 67, Folder 26)
    - Joint Council 53 Campaign, 1996; Series 8 Subseries 2 (Box 67, Folder 27)
    - Hoffa/South Jersey, 1996; Series 8 Subseries 2 (Box 67, Folder 28)
    - Hoffa/Ryan, 1996; Series 8 Subseries 2 (Box 67, Folder 29)
    - Response to National Stewards Mailing- 776, 1996; Series 8 Subseries 2 (Box 67, Folder 30)
    - Central Pennsylvania- Address List, 1996; Series 8 Subseries 2 (Box 67, Folder 31)